name: Spigot API
authors:
  - mfnalex
questions:
  - question: "What's the lowest possible \"api-version\" in plugin.yml?"
    answers:
      - "1.13"
  - question: "Custom Events require both, a static and a non-static method that return the HandlerList. The static method is called \"getHandlerList\". What's the non-static method called?"
    answers:
      - "getHandlers"
      - "getHandlers()"
  - question: "The second-last EventPriority is ..."
    answers:
      - "HIGHEST"
  - question: "The Spigot .jar is a bootstrap .jar since which version?"
    answers:
      - "1.18"
  - question: "The Bukkit API (as of version 1.19) requires at least which version of Java?"
    answers:
      - "8"
      - "1.8"
  - question: "Classes belonging to the vanilla server code are commonly referred to as what?"
    answers:
      - "NMS"
  - question: "Many CraftBukkit classes are wrappers for the underlying NMS classes. What's the method to get the NMS instance of the wrapped object?"
    answers:
      - "getHandle"
      - "getHandle()"
  - question: "To get a String from your config.yml, you can use getConfig().getString(...). In what class is the getString method declared?"
    answers:
      - "ConfigurationSection"
      - "org.bukkit.configuration.ConfigurationSection"
      - "MemorySection"
      - "org.bukkit.configuration.MemorySection"
  - question: "The Bukkit API provides an interface for serializable objects. What's the name of the interface?"
    answers:
      - "ConfigurationSerializable"
      - "org.bukkit.configuration.serialization.ConfigurationSerializable"
  - question: "The \"libraries\" feature in plugin.yml was added in which version?"
    answers:
      - "1.16.5"
  - question: "The PersistentDataContainer was added in which version?"
    answers:
      - "1.14.1"
  - question: "Since what version do Chunks implement PersistentDataHolder?"
    answers:
      - "1.16.3"
  - question: "What interface combines both TabCompleter and CommandExecutor?"
    answers:
      - "TabExecutor"
      - "org.bukkit.command.TabExecutor"
  - question: "Which class represents a rectangular box?"
    answers:
      - "BoundingBox"
      - "org.bukkit.util.BoundingBox"
  - question: "How many PersistentDataTypes does the Bukkit API provide?"
    answers:
      - "12"
      - "twelve"
  - question: "How many methods does the Listener interface declare?"
    answers:
      - "None"
      - "0"
      - "zero"
  - question: "Which event is called when a hopper tries to move items from one inventory to another?"
    answers:
      - "InventoryMoveItemEvent"
      - "InventoryMoveItem"
      - "org.bukkit.event.inventory.InventoryMoveItemEvent"
  - question: "The implementation of the PluginManager interface is called ..."
    answers:
      - "SimplePluginManager"
      - "org.bukkit.plugin.SimplePluginManager"
  - question: "LivingEntity#rayTraceBlocks(...) returns an instance of what class?"
    answers:
      - "RayTraceResult"
      - "org.bukkit.util.RayTraceResult"
  - question: "In plugin.yml, at least the following attributes have to be defined: main, name, and ..."
    answers:
      - "version"
  - question: "Valid values for the \"load\" attribute in plugin.yml are STARTUP and ..."
    answers:
      - "POSTWORLD"
  - question: "The opposite of \"softdepend\" in plugin.yml is called ..."
    answers:
      - "loadbefore"